# MICHAEL MOLINA

# **COMPUTER ENGINEER & WEB DEVELOPER**

# CONTACT

+52 7714141066



michaelmolina679@gmail.com



michaelmolina.me

## SKILLS

- Web Development
- ux / ui
- SCRUM
- Teamwork
- Git / Github
- Creative
- Reliable and Professional
- Organized
- Fast Learner
- Passion for Technology

# LANGUAGES

**NATIVE SPANISH** 

**ADVANCED ENGLISH** 

#### **PROFILE**

Mexican web developer, with 2 years of experience making web pages and web applications using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JS, Tailwind and React. I am currently looking for a job where I can contribute my knowledge and continue to improve my skills as a developer.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BALCHÉ NIKTÉ - SITIO WEB**

Independent Project | May 2020 - Agust 2020

Design and development of a website focused on skin care products, for a local company with the following technologies HTML, CSS, Tailwind

https://torpid-hot-socks.glitch.me/

#### **HACKATHON APP**

Leia MX | January 2019 - December 2019

Design and development of an application that would serve as a tool for the creation and management of hackathons in their own company.

It was made it with HTML, CSS and Javascript

### **TLALI**

University of Hidalgo State | April 2018 - Jun 2019

- Development of a multi-platform application for the monitoring and maintenance of a bio-intensive orchard. In Ionic
- I develop an API for the collection and storage of these data in a database in the cloud. In Laravel

# **EDUCATION**

## **COMPUTER ENGINEER**

UAEH - University of Hidalgo State | 2015 - 2019

#### **PROGRAMMING TECHNICIAN**

CECyTEM

| 2012 - 2015